adspreemedia.com 2018-02-07

# Privacy Policy | adspree media

adspree media GmbH is committed to protecting your privacy and creating a strong relationship with our users. Find our full contact details [here](http://adspreemedia.com/imprint).

This Privacy Policy explains the use of personal information collected via our websites, whether at adspreemedia.com or other uniform resource locators (URLs) owned or operated by us (all together hereinafter referred to as our "Website").

As used in this Privacy Policy, "personal information" means information about you that is personally identifiable, such as your name, e-mail address, phone number or physical address.

1.  **Contact**

If you have any questions, comments or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy or practices, please send an e-mail to info@adspreemedia.com.

2. **Information That We Collect**

We may collect different personal information from you when you use our Website. The following are examples to help you better understand the types of information that we collect.

_Information That You Provide Directly_

Use of our Website is generally possible without providing personal data. Personal data is only collected when necessary, for technical reasons regarding the use of our Website, or if you use certain functions such as contact forms. In these cases, it is necessary that you provide certain information and send it to us.

Please note that filling out mandatory fields in contact forms may be a form of data collection and that these fields are marked accordingly. Mandatory fields must be filled out before you can submit your request. The information provided in the required fields is used solely for the stated purpose and only with the available data you have freely provided us with. All other information is voluntary and will be used solely to process your request, for statistical internal purposes or to improve our service to you.

_Information Collected Through Technology_

The following data is collected automatically every time you access our Website:

  * Date and time of access
  * Name of the requested file
  * Website/URL that has been requested from the file
  * Access status (e.g., file transfer, file not found)
  * The internet browser you are using and the operating system of your device
  * The IP address of the requesting device

This data is logged anonymously. Your IP address will be shortened so that no associations to your person are possible. The anonymised logs are then processed exclusively for statistical purposes, comparison with other data sources and are not passed on to third parties.

3\. **Cookies**

We may use cookies to track general, non-personal information about our users for statistical and market research purposes (e.g., user name, pages viewed, time spent on applications, websites visited just before and just after our Services, etc.). This information is collected on an aggregated and anonymous basis.

4.  **Google Maps**

On the contact page, we use Google Maps to display geographical information. Google Maps is a map service from Google Inc. (“Google”). In order for Google Maps to be integrated and displayed in your internet browser, your browser must establish a connection to a Google server, which might be located in the United States of America. Google obtains the information that the contact page of our Website has been accessed by your IP address.

5.  **Disclosure Of Information To Third Parties**

Your information will never be disclosed to third parties, unless we are legally obliged to do so or you have explicitly consented to the disclosure of your data beforehand.

6.  **Security Of Your Information**

We are committed to safeguarding your information, and we implement reasonable security measures to protect the security of your information. We also constantly update our technology with the goal of better protecting your information.

While we take reasonable precautions against possible security breaches, no website or Internet transmission is completely secure, and we cannot guarantee that unauthorized access, hacking, data loss, or other breaches will not occur. We urge you to take steps to keep your personal information safe, to use strong passwords, to log out of your account after use, and to use different passwords for different services with different companies. It is important that you also help protect and maintain the security of your account. Please notify us immediately of any unauthorized use.

7.  **Deleting Your Information**

Your information will be deleted as soon as it is no longer needed for the above-mentioned purposes. Should it be required by law that certain data is retained, this data will be blocked. The data is then no longer available for further use.

8.  **Changes To This Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to update and modify this Privacy Policy at any time, which means that you should review this Privacy Policy from time to time to keep you informed on possible changes.

9.  **Rights Of Access And Revocation**

You have the right to request information about the data stored with us regarding your person at any time. If you have given us express consent to use your data, you can revoke at any time. Please submit any requests for access to your personal data in writing to info@adspreemedia.com. For further contact details see the [imprint](http://adspreemedia.com/imprint) on this Website.
